brokensilenze.net 2015-05-29

# PRIVACY POLICY | BrokenSilenze.net

### Privacy Policy:

BrokenSilenze.net (“ **BrokenSilenze.net** “) operates BrokenSilenze.net and may operate other websites. It is BrokenSilenze.net policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, BrokenSilenze.net collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. BrokenSilenze.net purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how BrokenSilenze.net visitors use its website. From time to time, BrokenSilenze.net may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

BrokenSilenze.net also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on BrokenSilenze.net blogs/sites. BrokenSilenze.net only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to BrokenSilenze.net websites choose to interact with BrokenSilenze.net in ways that require BrokenSilenze.net to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that BrokenSilenze.net gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [BrokenSilenze.net](http://brokensilenze.net/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with BrokenSilenze.net are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, BrokenSilenze.net collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with BrokenSilenze.net. BrokenSilenze.net does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

BrokenSilenze.net may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. BrokenSilenze.net may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, BrokenSilenze.net does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

BrokenSilenze.net discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on BrokenSilenze.net behalf or to provide services available at BrokenSilenze.net websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using BrokenSilenze.net websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. BrokenSilenze.net will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, BrokenSilenze.net discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when BrokenSilenze.net believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of BrokenSilenze.net, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an BrokenSilenze.net website and have supplied your email address, BrokenSilenze.net may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with BrokenSilenze.net and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. BrokenSilenze.net takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by BrokenSilenze.net and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, BrokenSilenze.net may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in BrokenSilenze.net sole discretion. BrokenSilenze.net encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a BrokenSilenze.net account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
